import { combineReducers } from 'redux'

const quiz = (
  state = {
    animals: [
      {
        questionNumber: 1,
        question: 'The heart of a shrimp is located at his:',
        answers: ['Chest', 'Legs', 'Head', 'Stomach'],
        rightAnswer: 'Head',
        hint: 'No hint available for this question',
      },
      {
        questionNumber: 2,
        question: 'A snail can sleep for?',
        answers: ['3 days', '3 weeks', '3 months', '3 years'],
        rightAnswer: '3 years',
        hint: 'Still not longer than Rotem :)',
      },
      {
        questionNumber: 3,
        question:
          'The fingerprints of what animal are almost identical to humans?',
        answers: ['Koala', 'Monkey', 'kangaroo', 'Lizard'],
        rightAnswer: 'Koala',
        hint:
          'Their fingerprints are so indistinguishable from humans that they have been confused at crime scenes',
      },
      {
        questionNumber: 4,
        question: 'How many noses do Slugs have?',
        answers: ['One', 'Two', 'Three', 'Four'],
        rightAnswer: 'Four',
        hint: 'No hint available for this question',
      },
      {
        questionNumber: 5,
        question:
          "Which one of these animals is the only animal that can't jump?",
        answers: ['Ostrich', 'Elephant', 'Rhino', 'Hippopotamus'],
        rightAnswer: 'Elephant',
        hint: 'Jumping is literally defying gravity!',
      },
      {
        questionNumber: 6,
        question: "A rhino's horn is made out of:",
        answers: ['Hair', 'Bacteria', 'Sand', 'Muscle Tissue'],
        rightAnswer: 'Hair',
        hint: 'Giving a hint would not be FAIR',
      },
      {
        questionNumber: 7,
        question: 'How much time does it take a sloth to digest its food?',
        answers: ['2 Minutes', '2 Hours', '2 Days', '2 Weeks'],
        rightAnswer: '2 Weeks',
        hint: 'Sloths are very slow...',
      },
      {
        questionNumber: 8,
        question: "Which animal doesn't have vocal cords?",
        answers: ['Zebra', 'Giraffe', 'Beetle', 'Mantis'],
        rightAnswer: 'Giraffe',
        hint: 'No hint available for this question',
      },
    ],
    drinks: {},
    food: {},
    computers: [
      {
        questionNumber: 1,
        question:
          'How long did it take to create the language known today as "Javascript"?',
        answers: ['10 days', '10 weeks', '10 months', '3 years'],
        rightAnswer: '10 days',
        hint: 'The language was developed by 1 person.',
      },
      {
        questionNumber: 2,
        question:
          'What year was the language known today as "Javascript" created?',
        answers: ['1934', '1955', '1978', '2000'],
        rightAnswer: '1955',
        hint:
          'The language was developed at a company called "NETSCAPE" which has launched the first ever web browser.',
      },
      {
        questionNumber: 3,
        question:
          'What was the first name that was given to the language known today as "Javascript"?',
        answers: ['Mocha', 'ECMAScript', 'LiveScript', 'JScript'],
        rightAnswer: 'Mocha',
        hint:
          'They are all names that were given to the language during its lifetime, but only one of them was the first.',
      },
      {
        questionNumber: 4,
        question: 'How many percentage of the web is built using Javascript?',
        answers: ['50%', '65%', '80%', '95%'],
        rightAnswer: '95%',
        hint: 'Javascript is the standard programming language for the web',
      },
      {
        questionNumber: 5,
        question: 'What language do computers speak in?',
        answers: ['English', 'Only numbers', "Only 1's and 0's", 'Latin'],
        rightAnswer: "Only 1's and 0's",
        hint:
          "The computer's language is limited by the current technology used to build them.",
      },
      {
        questionNumber: 6,
        question: 'When was the first computer built?',
        answers: ['1801', '1833', '1899', '1913'],
        rightAnswer: '1833',
        hint:
          'Charles Babbage, an english mechanic and mathematician, originated the concept of a programmable computer.',
      },
      {
        questionNumber: 7,
        question: 'How many MAIN parts do computers have?',
        answers: ['5', '7', '9', '11'],
        rightAnswer: '5',
        hint:
          'One of the main parts of a computer is the CPU (Central Processing Unit) that is in charge of all of computations and calculations, and can access all of the other parts of the computer, like the RAM (Random Access Memory).',
      },
      {
        questionNumber: 8,
        question: 'How much money does the average Software Engineer make?',
        answers: [
          '72,000$ Per year',
          '83,000$ Per year',
          '97,000$ Per year',
          '110,000$ Per year',
        ],
        rightAnswer: '110,000$ Per year',
        hint:
          'They make a TON of money. and 1 Dollar is roughly equivalent to 3.5 Shekels.',
      },
    ],
  },
  { type, payload }
) => {
  switch (type) {
    default:
      return state
  }
}

const todosReducer = (
  state = {
    todosApp: {
      todos: [],
      savedTodos: [],
      inputValue: '',
    },
  },
  { type, payload }
) => {
  switch (type) {
    case 'ADD_TODO':
      return {
        ...state,
        todosApp: {
          todos: [...state.todosApp.todos, payload],
          inputValue: '',
          savedTodos: [...state.todosApp.savedTodos],
        },
      }
    case 'DELETE_TODO':
      return {
        ...state,
        todosApp: {
          todos: [
            ...state.todosApp.todos.filter(todo => {
              return todo.id !== payload
            }),
          ],
          inputValue: state.todosApp.inputValue,
          savedTodos: [...state.todosApp.savedTodos],
        },
      }
    case 'SAVE_TODO':
      return {
        ...state,
        todosApp: {
          todos: [
            ...state.todosApp.todos.map(todo =>
              state.todosApp.todos[payload] === todo
                ? { ...todo, isSaved: true }
                : todo
            ),
          ],
          inputValue: state.todosApp.inputValue,
          savedTodos: [
            ...state.todosApp.savedTodos,
            state.todosApp.todos[payload],
          ],
        },
      }
    case 'DELETE_SAVED_TODO':
      return {
        ...state,
        todosApp: {
          todos: [...state.todosApp.todos],
          inputValue: state.todosApp.inputValue,
          savedTodos: [
            ...state.todosApp.savedTodos.filter(savedTodo => {
              return savedTodo !== state.todosApp.savedTodos[payload]
            }),
          ],
        },
      }
    case 'TOGGLE_TODO':
      return {
        ...state,
        todosApp: {
          todos: [
            ...state.todosApp.todos.map(todo => {
              if (todo.id === payload) {
                return { ...todo, isCompleted: !todo.isCompleted }
              } else {
                return todo
              }
            }),
          ],
          inputValue: state.todosApp.inputValue,
          savedTodos: [...state.todosApp.savedTodos],
        },
      }
    case 'ADD_TODO_FROM_SAVED':
      return {
        ...state,
        todosApp: {
          todos: [...state.todosApp.todos, state.todosApp.savedTodos[payload]],
          inputValue: state.todosApp.inputValue,
          savedTodos: [...state.todosApp.savedTodos],
        },
      }
    case 'CHANGE_INPUT_VALUE':
      return {
        ...state,
        todosApp: {
          todos: [...state.todosApp.todos],
          inputValue: payload,
          savedTodos: [...state.todosApp.todos],
        },
      }
    default:
      return state
  }
}

const reducer = combineReducers({
  quiz,
  todosReducer,
})

export default reducer
